Guide to the Amos Poe Papers, 1966-2005 MSS.203
Fales Library and Special Collections
Amos Poe Papers
1966-2005
Fales Library and Special Collections
Poe, Amos
MSS.203
133.5 Linear Feet in 68 boxes; film, video, and audio elements.
Amos Poe is a filmmaker, writer, and producer who became one of the leading figures of the No Wave Cinema Movement (1976-1985). The Amos Poe Papers largely preserves Poe's writing and the writing of others, which includes scripts, screenplays, and other writings, as well as journals, notebooks, photographs, and audio and moving image elements.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers without restriction.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Amos Poe in 2007, with accretions to the collection received in 2009 and 2016. The accession numbers associated with these gifts are 2007.203, 2009.203, and 2016.044, respectively.
Arrangement
Within each series, materials are arranged alphabetically by project title, then chronologically if dated. In some cases, which are indicated, the material was arranged by Poe and has retained its original organization.
Series I: Writing includes the work of Amos Poe and others, it is organized alphabetically by document title, then chronologically.
Subseries A: Scripts and Screenplays
Subseries B: Film Treatments, Notes, and Notebooks This subseries includes notation and development directly related to the previous subseries.
Subseries C: Source and Subject Files This subseries consists of documentation directly related to the previous subseries, in addition to development files dedicated to individuals of interest, as either source material or collaborative parties.
Subseries D: Miscellaneous This subseries includes material that is not directly related to Poe's film career, consisting of student essays, notebooks, articles, lyrics, poetry, and development of the graphic novel "La Pacifica."
Series II: Production Files documents the production development of films and music videos involving Poe. Elements are organized by document type, alphabetically by project title, and then chronologically.
Subseries A: Administrative This subseries includes pre-production materials: casting, contact lists, shooting schedules, and miscellaneous office management documentation.
Subseries B: Financial This subseries exclusively holds budgetary documentation, cost reports, and cash flow estimates.
Subseries C: Distribution and Promotion This subseries consists of press pack materials, critical reviews, screening information, and sales agreements and reports.
Subseries D: Film Festivals This subseries includes festivals that screened Poe's work and festivals or events of interest. These contents are organized alphabetically by project title or film festival, then chronologically.
Subseries E: Project Correspondence This subseries consists of communication directly related to the previous subseries. Documents are organized alphabetically by individual or corporation in contact.
Series III: Press includes press about Amos Poe as a filmmaker, but is not directly promotional for any single project individually. This documentation is organized alphabetically by periodical or article title.
Subseries A: About Amos Poe
Subseries B: Clips of Interest
Series IV: Teaching Materials documents Amos Poe the educator. These elements are organized alphabetically by class title or name of institution, then chronologically.
Subseries A: Course Components This subseries includes syllabi, class lists, and teaching contracts.
Subseries B: Miscellaneous Reading This subseries includes articles and literature excerpts not directly related to any single course, and is organized alphabetically by document title.
Series V: Correspondence includes communication not directly related to any single production, and is organized alphabetically by individual or corportation in contact, then chronologically.
Subseries A: Professional
Subseries B: Personal
Series VI: Photography includes photographs, contact sheets, negatives, and slides pertaining to Poe's professional work and personal collection.
Subseries A: Amos Poe Productions This subseries includes stills, negatives, and contact sheets related to Series II. These elements are organized alphabetically by production title.
Subseries B: Other Productions This subseries includes stills from productions not by Amos Poe, which are organized alphabetically by production title.
Subseries C: Talent Files This subseries includes miscellaneous headshots, resumes, and talent agency catalogs in their original organization by Poe. These materials are not in any particular order and are not attached to any single production. Similar elements are located in Series II: Production Files, subseries A: Administrative, which are organized by production title or production company, either "Amos Poe Productions" or "Rain Film."
Subseries D: Personal This subseries includes photographs, negatives, contact sheets, and slides either unlabelled or not directly related to any specific production. These elements are organized alphabetically by original title or date. In addition, this subseries includes three binders of unidentified photographic elements in no particular order.
Series VII: Visual Materials includes scrapbooks, posters and artwork by Amos Poe and others.
Subseries A: Scrapbooks
Subseries B: Posters and Artwork
Series VIII: Film includes original filmic elements by Amos Poe. Access copies appropriate for consultation may not be available, please ask a Fales archivist.
Subseries A: Access Copies
Subseries B: Originals
Subseries C: Film Documentation
Series IX: Video
Access copies appropriate for consultation may not be available, please ask a Fales archivist.
Subseries A: Access Copies
Subseries B: Originals
Subseries C: Miscellaneous Video
Series X: Audio
Access copies appropriate for consultation may not be available, please ask a Fales archivist.
Subseries A: Access Copies
Subseries B: Originals
Subseries C: Miscellaneous Audio
Series XI: Objects includes office items, buttons and other collectables.
Series XII: Data Storage includes magnetic and optical computer elements.
Biographical Note
Amos Poe (Amos Jay Porges) was born in Tel Aviv in 1949, and his family emigrated to the United States in 1957. The Russian invasion of Czechoslovakia provided a source for his first photographic series in 1968. His film career began in the early 1970s, when he made his first Super-8 films and briefly worked in distribution. Poe became one of the leading figures of the No Wave Cinema Movement (1976-1985) that developed out the New York East Village music and art community, which included Jim Jarmusch, Eric Mitchell, Beth B and Scott B, Vivienne Dick, John Lurie, Becky Johnston, James Nares and Nick Zedd. This movement embraced the artistic sensibilities of the avant-garde, French New Wave, and B-Movie genres. It was also during this period that Poe contributed writing and photography to publications specific to this scene, including NY Rocker and Traveler's Digest.
As a filmmaker, Poe sites the work of Jean-Luc Godard, John Cassavettes, and Andy Warhol as primary influences. In 1975, Poe collaborated with artist Ivan Kral (bassist of The Patti Smith Group) to create "The Blank Generation," which includes early performances of Iggy Pop, Blondie, Patti Smith, Television, Richard Hell and the Heartbreakers, The Ramones, Talking Heads, and Wayne County. Beginning in 1976, Poe experimented with the theme of alienating modernity amid new environments in his next three films, "Unmade Beds," (1976) "The Foreigner," (1978) and "Subway Riders" (1981). "Unmade Beds" is an homage to Godard's "Breathless" while "The Foreigner," starring Eric Mitchell and Debbie Harry, shares sensibilities with Jim Jarmusch's "Permanent Vacation" and Susan Seidelman's "Smithereens."
Poe's most widely distributed film, "Alphabet City" (1985) starred Vincent Spano, Kate Vernon, and Jamie Gertz. It was also during this time that Poe directed music videos for artists such as Run DMC and Anthrax. During 1985-1986, Poe wrote "Rocket Gibraltar," which was Burt Lancaster's first film and Macauley Culkin, Kevin Spacey, and Bill Pullman's debut film. During 1988-1990 Poe wrote a number of unproduced screenplays including "Port of Call," "The Golden Eagle," "Mrs. Dogg," "Beach House," and "Paint It Black." The production of "Triple Bogey On A Five Par Hole" marked Poe's official return to independent filmmaking in 1990. With Dolly Hall, he produced Steven Starr's "Joey Breaker," which starred Richard Edson, Gina Gershon, and Phillip Seymour Hoffman in 1992.
1993-1994 was another prolific writing period for Poe in which he completed "Kid Killer," "La Pacifica," "The Guitar," "Lodz Seven," "The Grey Nun," "Hard on Berlin," and "The Listener." In 1994 with novelist Joel Rose, Poe co-wrote and directed Stephen Baldwin and Bai Ling in the Ed Wood inspired sci-fi fantasy, "Dead Weekend." In 1998, Poe wrote and directed "Frogs For Snakes" starring Barbara Hershey, Robbie Coltrane, Ian Hart, Debi Mazar, Harry Hamlin, Clarence William III, Lisa Marie, and John Leguizamo. In 1998-1999 Poe completed "Stunning," "To Kill An Angel," "Underage" (with Dirk Wittenborn), "Bypass" and "The Night Witches." Also during this period, Poe directed videos for singer-songwriter Steve Earle and later directed and produced a portrait of the same artist, "Steve Earle: Just An American Boy" (2003). Current projects include an interpretation of Andy Warhol's "Empire" and an online, proactive platform for filmmakers, designers and artists called "Pianospecs." Poe resides in New York City with his wife, artist Sarah Charlesworth, and teaches screenplay development and experimental production at New York University's Tisch School of the Arts.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access copies for audiovisual materials in the collection are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact fales.library@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Scope and Content
The Amos Poe Papers contain materials that directly relate to his film career, ranging from the late 1970s through 2005. In addition, this collection largely preserves Poe's writing and the writing of others, which includes scripts, screenplays, treatments and rewrites, articles, essays, short stories, journals, notebooks, a graphic novel, lyrics, and poetry, that occasionally date back to Poe's high school and collegiate education that began in the 1960s. Elements include source material for projects that progressed beyond the writing stage. This body of components includes pre-production agreements and budgetary reports, on-set schedules and memorandums, distribution and promotional materials, teaching elements, professional and personal correspondence, production and personal photography, original artwork, scrapbooks, and original film, video, and audio recordings.
Alphabet City (Motion picture); Blank Generation (Motion picture); Scrapbooks.; Correspondence.; Scripts (documents); Punk culture -- New York (State) -- New York; Screenplays; Independent filmmakers -- United States.; Super 8; Videocassettes.; Promotional materials; Photographs.; 16mm; Experimental films; Ramones (Musical group); Kral, Ivan; Hannah, Duncan; Mitchell, Eric; Sellers, Terence; Hell, Richard; Poe, Amos
- Series I: Writing
  - Series I, Subseries A: Scripts and Screenplays
    - "Acme Rainbow" [with Notation for John Heyman], c1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - "Agent Breaker" by Steven Starr [1st Draft with Notes], August 25, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - "Agent Breaker" by Steven Starr [Revised Fragments, 4th Draft], October 1, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - "Agent Breaker"/ "Brokedown Palace" by Steven Starr, August 4, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - "(Joey) Breaker" [Script with Annotation], August 18 [no year] (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - "All I Do Is Think About You (The Peg Leg Story)" by Nick Poe [Script with Production Plan], undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - "Alphabet City: Amos' Pink Script", September 13, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - "Alphabet City" [Full Script with Annotation], c1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - "Alphabet City" by Gregory Heller and Amos Poe [Revised Version #1], September 19, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - "Alphabet City" by Gregory Heller and Amos Poe [Revised Version with Annotation], September 19, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - "Alphabet City" by Gregory Heller and Amos Poe [1st Draft with Annotation], undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - "Alphabet City: Gregory's Original Script, Andrew #3", undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - "Alphabet City: Gregory's Original Script, Roberta #2" [With Annotation], undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - "Alphabet City" [Original with Annotation], undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - "Alphabet City" [Early Draft], undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - "Alphaville" by Jean-Luc Godard [English Translation and Description of Action by Peter Whitehead], c1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - "Beach House / The Big Secret/ The Big Weekend" by Amos Poe [With Annotation], 1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - "Beach House" by Amos Poe [With Annotation and Related Paper Elements], c1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - "Beach House" by Amos Poe [1st Draft with Annotation], undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - "Beach House" by Amos Poe and Susan Davis [Handwritten], undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - "Beach House" by Amos Poe, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - "Berlin" by Amos Poe and Terence Sellers [1st Draft with Annotation], 1982 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - "Berlin" by Amos Poe and Terence Sellers [2nd Draft], 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - "Berlin" by Amos Poe and Terence Sellers [2nd Draft with Images], 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - "The Bros. Bouley" by Amos Poe, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - "Bypass" by Amos Poe [With Annotation], July 16, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - "By-Pass" by Amos Poe, July 22, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - "By-Pass" by Amos Poe, August 17, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - "By-Pass" by Amos Poe, August 25, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - "Bypass" by Amos Poe, October 17, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - "Bypass" [based on "The Heart Surgeon" by John Collee], October 26, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - "Bypass" [Draft with Assorted Feeback and Annotation], c1999 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - "Bypass" by Amos Poe, November 1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - "Bypass" by Amos Poe [Full Script with John Heyman's Notes], October 27, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - "Bypass" by Amos Poe, October 29, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - "Bypass" by Amos Poe, November 2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - "Bypass" by Amos Poe, March 2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - "Bypass" by Amos Poe [With Annotation], Spring 2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - "Bypass" by Amos Poe, Spring 2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "Bypass" by Amos Poe [Revised Draft], June 2001 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - "Bypass" by Amos Poe [Revised Draft], August 2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - "Bypass" by Amos Poe [Revised Draft with Annotation], October 2001 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      General
      The white paper elements in this document represent locations of note. Please do not remove.
    - "Bypass" by Amos Poe [Revised Draft with Annotation], November 2001 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - "Bypass" by Amos Poe [Revised Draft], November 2001 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - "Bypass" [Fragments], undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - "Bypass" [Fragments with Annotation], undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - "Chez Brigitte" by Sandrine Muller and Amos Poe, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - "Cleaver's Last Stand" by Meghan A. Leon, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - "Clockers" by Richard Price [1st Draft], June 25, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - "Copperhead Road (Suffolk County)" by Abdul O'Toole, February 2001 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - "Crack-Up" by Abdul O'Toole, March 2001 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - "The Cure For Love" by Amos Poe [Partial], February 1996 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - "Dead Weekend" by Joel Rose, October 1992 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - "Dead Weekend" by Joel Rose [1st Draft], October 1992 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - "Dead Weekend" by Joel Rose [With Annotation], October 1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - "Dead Weekend" Screenplay by Joel Rose, Story by Amos Poe, July 1993 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - "Dead Weekend" Screenplay by Joel Rose, Story by Amos Poe, July 1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - "Dead Weekend" Screenplay by Joel Rose, Story by Amos Poe [With Annotation], July 1993 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - "Dead Weekend" Screenplay by Joel Rose, Story by Amos Poe [2nd Draft], May 1994 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - "Dead Weekend / Alien Honey" Screenplay by Joel Rose, Story by Amos Poe [2nd Draft with Annotation], May 1994 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - "Dead Weekend" Screenplay by Joel Rose, Story by Amos Poe [The Final Draft], September 1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - "Dead Weekend" Screenplay by Joel Rose, Story by Amos Poe ["The Draft"], undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - "Deer Isle" by Amos Poe, March 2002 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "Deer Isle" by Amos Poe [With Annotation], 2002 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - "Deer Isle" by Amos Poe, June 2003 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - "Deer Isle" by Amos Poe [Partial], June 2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - "Die Tomorrow" by Amos Poe, January 1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - "Die Tomorrow" by Amos Poe, January 1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - "Die Tomorrow" by Amos Poe [With Annotation], January 1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - "Die Tomorrow" [Fragments and Notes], undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - "The Dinner Party" by Martin Thau [With Annotation], undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - "Down on Ponce" A Screenplay based on the book by Fred Willard, Written by Michael Simpson [With Annotation], April 16, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - "Drop A Dime" by Scott Lerner [With Notes], 1990 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - "Fish Belly White" by Michael Burke, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - "The Foreigner" [Early Draft, Partial], undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" by Amos Poe, July 1996 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" by Amos Poe [II], July 1996 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - "Generous Heart, Inc." Screenplay by Ian Kessner and Amos Poe [Draft I with Annotation], April 1995 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - "Generous Heart Inc." Screenplay by Ian Kessner and Amos Poe [Draft I with Annotation], April 1995 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - "Generous Heart" Screenplay by Amos Poe and Ian Kessner, May 1995 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - "Generous Heart" by Amos Poe and Ian Kessner [Draft II, Partial], July 1995 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - "Generous Heart" Screenplay by Amos Poe and Ian Kessner [Draft 09/95], September 1995 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - "Generous Heart" Screenplay by Amos Poe and Ian Kessner [Draft I], October 27, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - "Generous Heart" Screenplay by Amos Poe and Ian Kessner [Partial with Annotation], June 1995 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - "Generous Heart" Screenplay by Amos Poe and Ian Kessner, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - "Generous Heart" [Under Review, Partial], undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - "Golden Eagle" Screenplay by Amos Poe [2nd Draft with Annotation], January 1991 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - "The Golden Eagle" Screenplay by Amos Poe [2nd Draft], March 1991 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - "The Golden Eagle" Screenplay by Amos Poe [2nd Draft], March 1991 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - "The Golden Eagle" Screenplay by Amos Poe [Full Script with Outline-Synopsis and Notes], undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - "The Grey Nun" Screenplay by Amos Poe and Joel Rose [With Annotation], 1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - "The Grey Nun" Screenplay by Amos Poe and Joel Rose [With Annotation], 1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - "The Grey Nun" Screenplay by Amos Poe and Joel Rose, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - "The Grey Nun" Screenplay by Amos Poe and Joel Rose, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - "The Guitar" by I.B. Specter [With Annotation], March 1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - "The Guitar" by Amos Poe [2nd Draft], April 1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - "The Guitar" by Amos Poe [Revised 3/96], March 1996 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - "The Guitar" by Amos Poe, September 9, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - "The Guitar" by Amos Poe, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - "The Guitar" by Amos Poe, December 2000 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - "The Guitar" by Amos Poe, December 2000 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - "The Guitar" by Amos Poe [With Annotation], May 2003 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      The white paper elements in this document indicate locations of note. Please do not remove.
    - "The Guitar" by Amos Poe [#1], undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - "The Guitar" by Amos Poe, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - "Hard On Berlin" by Amos Poe, February 29, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - "Hard On Berlin" by Amos Poe, February 1992 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - "Hard On Berlin" by Amos Poe, February 1992 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - "Hard On Berlin" by Amos Poe, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - "Hard On Berlin" by Amos Poe [With Annotation and Inserts], undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - "Hard On Berlin" by Amos Poe, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - "The Hat Man" by Abdul O'Toole, March 2001 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - "The Heart Surgeon" by John Collee and Amos Poe [2nd Version], April 1999 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - "The Heart Surgeon" by John Collee and Amos Poe, May 1999 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - "The Heart Surgeon" by John Collee and Amos Poe [With Annotation], May 1999 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - "The Heart Surgeon" by John Collee and Amos Poe [With Annotation and Memos], May 1999 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - "The Heart Surgeon" by John Collee and Amos Poe, June 1999 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - "The Heart Surgeon" by John Collee and Amos Poe, July 18, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - "The Heart Surgeon" by John Collee and Amos Poe [With Annotation], undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - "The Heart Surgeon" by John Collee and Amos Poe [With Annotation], undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - "The Heart Surgeon" by John Collee [Episode 1 of 4], undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - "The Heart Surgeon" by John Collee [Episode 2 of 4], undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - "The Heart Surgeon" by John Collee [Episode 3 of 4], undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - "The Heart Surgeon" by John Collee [Episode 4 of 4], undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - "Hearts/On/Fire" by Amos Poe and Ian Kessner [With Annotation], May 1996 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - "Hearts On Fire" by Amos Poe and Ian Kessner [2nd Draft], September 30, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - "The Hole" / "Short Lives" by Guido Chiesa and Terri Jentz [With Annotation], 1986 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - "The Hole" by Amos Poe [Handwritten], 1987 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - "The Hole" [With Annotation], undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - "Homesick" by Cookie Mueller, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - "Hop, Dip and Spin" by Amos Poe [With Annotation], August 1989 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - "Hop, Dip and Spin" / "The Grand Ball" by Amos Poe [Handwritten with Notes], 1989 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - "I.A.U. 'Honorable Men' " by Amos Poe, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - "I.A.U. 'Honorable Men' " by Amos Poe [Partial], undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - "Isle of Hope" by Srulik Wojnowich, October 28, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - "Jake Prince P.I." by Richard Edson, Amos Poe, and Joel Rose, June 27, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - "Jihad in Jersey" by Amos Poe and Marc Levin, March 2006 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - "Just Around the Corner to the Light of Day (aka 'Born in the U.S.A.)" by Paul Schrader, November 20, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - "Kenny Makes A Move" by Amos Poe and Brian Kistler [1st Draft], 2000 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - "Kenny Makes A Move" by Brian Kistler and Amos Poe, February 2001 (Box 5, Folder 22)